export const questions = [
    
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "((HEALTH ))Which article of the Indian Constitution guarantees the right to education for all children, including boys?",
    "options": ["Article 21", "Article 15", "Article 45", "Article 14"],
    "correctAnswer": "Article 21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of the government program launched in India to promote boys' education?",
    "options": ["Beti Bachao, Beti Padhao", "Sarva Shiksha Abhiyan", "Make in India", "Khelo India"],
    "correctAnswer": "Sarva Shiksha Abhiyan"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What percentage of seats in educational institutions are reserved for boys under the Right to Education Act in India?",
    "options": ["20%", "25%", "30%", "35%"],
    "correctAnswer": "No reservation for boys"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In which year was the Right of Children to Free and Compulsory Education Act (RTE) enacted in India?",
    "options": ["2005", "2010", "2015", "2020"],
    "correctAnswer": "2009"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which organization primarily oversees the implementation of boys' education initiatives in India?",
    "options": ["Ministry of Health and Family Welfare", "Ministry of Women and Child Development", "Ministry of Human Resource Development", "Ministry of Rural Development"],
    "correctAnswer": "Ministry of Human Resource Development"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the dropout rate among boys in India, according to recent statistics?",
    "options": ["20%", "30%", "40%", "50%"],
    "correctAnswer": "30%"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which Indian state has the highest male literacy rate?",
    "options": ["Kerala", "Bihar", "Uttar Pradesh", "Rajasthan"],
    "correctAnswer": "Kerala"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the primary reason for the low enrollment of boys in schools in rural areas of India?",
    "options": ["Lack of interest in education", "Poverty and financial constraints", "Inadequate school infrastructure", "Cultural norms and societal restrictions"],
    "correctAnswer": "Poverty and financial constraints"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which international organization has partnered with India to support boys' education initiatives?",
    "options": ["World Bank", "UNESCO", "UNICEF", "Asian Development Bank"],
    "correctAnswer": "UNESCO"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the name of the flagship scholarship program in India aimed at promoting higher education among boys from economically weaker sections?",
    "options": ["Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana", "Pragati Scholarship Scheme", "Beti Bachao, Beti Padhao", "Sukanya Samriddhi Yojana"],
    "correctAnswer": "Pragati Scholarship Scheme"
  }
  ];